## Wouter

# Meijer

houterm [at] gmail.com linkedin.com/in/wouterjmeijer portfolio: hOuter.github.io (WIP)

Summary

Working a business role at a scale-up allowed me to get hands-on experience with marketing, client-facing communications, stakeholder awareness and sales. These skills are complementary to my interdisciplinary engineering competencies as listed below. My main interests are with the cognitive aspects of robotics.

**Experience** 

### **Skelex - Business Development**

September 2018 - 2020, Rotterdam

I represented Skelex at numerous events and advised businesses on adopting exoskeleton technology in their workforce. Additionally I set up and orchestrated a campaign to raise exoskeleton awareness and find new customers in the Shipbuilding Sector. I supervised 3 groups of marketing interns to execute this campaign.

#### Freelance - Developer

June 2018 - present, Delft

One interesting project involved building a web calculator to calculate the ROI for refitting light sources with LED's in office buildings. This project was commissioned by a large light source manufacturer.

#### **Mechnificent - Treasurer**

March 2016 - Mar 2017, Delft

With a team of 6 Mechanical Engineering students orchestrate the logistics, location, safety and organisation of a party for 1250 students.

**Education** 

## Delft University of Technology - MSc. Cognitive Robotics

2019 - Present

Experience with: Machine & Deep Learning, Optimisation, Motion Planning, Machine Perception, Data Analysis & Visualisation, Signal Processing, System Identification, Filtering, Dynamics, Intelligent Vehicles, Man-Machine Interaction, Control, Neuromechanics.

## Delft University of Technology - BSc. Mechanical Engineering

2014 - 2019

Minor in Electrical & Biomedical Engineering Bachelor Final Project @ Systems & Control

## Stedelijk Gymnasium Haarlem - VWO NT/NG

2014

**Skills** 

English

• French, German, Spanish

Solidworks/CAD

Coding

Cambridge Advanced English

Basic

Mechanical Design - Associate level JavaScript (typescript, bootstrap)

Python (num.py, tf, plot.ly, pandas, scipy)

C++ (ROS, OpenCV, pcl)

Matlab